[
  {
    "question": "1 x 3",
    "options": ["2", "3", "4"],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 3",
    "options": ["4", "6", "8"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 3",
    "options": ["6", "9", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 3",
    "options": ["9", "12", "15"],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 3",
    "options": ["12", "15", "18"],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 3",
    "options": ["15", "18", "21"],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 3",
    "options": ["18", "21", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 3",
    "options": ["21", "24", "27"],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 3",
    "options": ["24", "27", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 3",
    "options": ["27", "30", "33"],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  }
]
